Subscribe to the YouTube channel
AllBankWater.com and press the bell button to
watch the video first.
Friends, in this video we will tell you
important information related to your IDFC Bank account. Today we will tell you
how you can transfer funds from the ICICI Bank mobile application.
For this, the iMobile application must be activated on your mobile
and you will login to this application by entering your
four digit login PIN on the
internet and in the fund
transfer option you will
add the account details here. See, you will see on the
add and management option,
going to this you have to add the account details
where you want to transfer the money.
You will see here there are two options
ICICI Bank and if it is a bank then
you will add the details of the account in which you want to transfer the money.
Above all you will enter the account number and after that the account
holder name and after that here the nick name
and then you will enter the life secure number here.
If you do not know the IFSC code
then you can also enter it and
after that you will click on the famous button. Now
you will see that you will receive an OTP.
Enter this OTP here and after that  After that,
on the next page, you will only be asked for the transfer amount. If
you want to transfer your amount here,
you will enter the interest and
click on the profit button.
After this, you will match the details and confirm it. Then it will
ask you for a four-digit login here. If you
type your login, your gold will be
successfully transferred. Friends,
now we will tell you that if you
transfer to Andhra Bank other than ICICI Bank, then how will you
take it. For this, you will see that the pay details you just
added will be shown in the playlist.
You will click on the account to which you want to transfer it.
After that, you will
add the amount at the top. Now you will see that the appointment is being made here.
You will select the mode through which you want to transfer the payment and
after that, you will transfer it. Friends, here
you get one more option. If you want to
transfer this quarter inch on a regular monthly basis, then
you can also set it on a monthly basis here,
so that every month your payment will be made on that date.
If you have to type
So one time or if you
want to print it, then after making a lipstick,
click on the process button
and after matching the details here,
click on the confirm button and you will
see that your fund transfer will be done successfully,
so friends, in this way you
can transfer funds here, if you have to do regular
transfer, like if
you click friend, then you
can also save it in favorites, friends,
if you liked this video, then like this
video and subscribe to our channel
because on this channel we keep
giving important information related to your health, so do subscribe to this channel
and share this video with your friends, so
friends, that's all for today, we will
meet in the next video, till then
bye-bye